

# CONTACT

**≥** brentjeremynel@gmail.com

+1 5615010926

(in) brent-jeremy-47172b22a

**S** @BrentJeremy3

Brent-Jeremy

O United State

# Languages

English

\_\_\_\_\_\_ 90% 'hai

100%

# Interest

Game: Fan

FOOTBALL: AMATEUR
Basketball: Amateur
Piano: Amateur

# **BRENT JEREMY**

# **Blockchain Developer**

Slogan: "Promise is law"

A proficient blockchain developer with 4 years of experience, interested in contributing expertise in web and blockchain development. Capable of excelling as part of a team or individually in a fast-paced environment. Deeply knowledgeable in distributed ledger, blockchain security, blockchain architecture patterns, and different blockchain standards and ecosystems. Also I worked as fullstack developer for about 9 years, So I am sure for all software development. Thanks for your checking my Resume.

## **Main Skills**

|                       | _  |
|-----------------------|--|
| Language              | Solidity,Web3,React,Python<br>Rust,Move  |
| Frameworks            | Express                                  |
| Cloud                 | AWS,Google                               |
| Database              | MySQL,MongoDB,AWS<br>Dynamodb,PostgreSQL |
| Methodologies         | Agile, Waterfall model,<br>Scrum         |
| DevOps Tool           | Docker,Kubernetes                        |
| Version Control Tools | GIT, SVN                                 |

## **EDUCATION**

King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### 01/2022 - 07/2022 WRINKLE WERX INC

United State Blockchain Developer

#### Forking the blockchain

https://deamchain.com/

- Involved in complete development of Agile Methodology. Participated in Scrum process that is used for planning different iterations of the project.
- Involved forking EVM comfortable blockchain and installed new blockchain with more than 20 validators.
- Launched new blockchain explorer such as BSC scan and ETH scan that was enabled to verify more than 10 smart contracts at one time.
- Used Ticketing tool JIRA for monitoring of work assignment, track defects and changes for change management with more than 5 testers
- Attended daily status meetings with the development, functional and project management teams to discuss status, project timelines and testing strategies.

#### 10/2021 - 12/2021 BABYLON

US Project manager

Casino game development

https://game.babylonswap.finance/

- Designed entire project for game platform and created 5 UML diagrams (Class diagram, Use Case Diagram, Communication diagram)
- Deployed 2 smart contracts that control the game, token staking and BEP-20 token and solana token.
- Built game backend to store user staking status, game status and logs. So we can improve game speed by 75% than the game with only smart contract
- Published about 9 casino games and integrated to our game platform.
- Launched smart contract with Solidity and Rust for the game.

#### 01/2021 - 10/2021 ACCUSOFT

Canada Frontend developer

#### Frontend development

https://learnt.io/

- Worked as frontend developer with React, AWS Amplify, Angular js for about 10 months
- Designed Blockchain landing pages and integrated with contract using web3.js ,web3-react module, use-wallet module and so on with about 4 backend developers.
- Enhanced legacy application by building new components in React and JavaScript resulted in 50% improvement in react design

#### 03/2020 - 12/2020 FREELANCER WORK

United state Fullstack and Blockchain developer

#### Work as Blockchain developer

- Worked in building DEFI for BEP-20 token and generated more than \$5000K+ in annual for the company
- Created a lot of smart contract for the dapp with solidity,Rust,Move.

# Golang backend and Node.js Thailand

#### **Work as Backend Developer**

- Rest Api and GraphQl api with Node is ,Django and .NET
- Java Spring site development
- AWS, Google Service and Azure Kubernets

#### **Work as Frontend Developer**

• Designed and developed the application using React framework along with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap

#### 03/2016 - 03/2020 PROLOCALIZE CO., LTD.

LeadEngineer

#### https://smartcat.com (CRM site using AWS,Node,react js)

- Administrated in **Agile** software development life cycle (SDLC) with SCRUM methodology.
- Established company own translator with **Django** using **AWS** SageMaker
- Developed CRM web site with Nodejs GraphQL api backend and react js frontend.
- Used AWS SNS to email, AWS appsync for GraphQL api implement, AWS  $S_3$  to manage assert files, AWS  $EC_2$  for
- Created customized AMIs based on already existing AWS EC2 instances by using create image functionality, hence using this snapshot for disaster recovery.